ethos.com.cn 2007-12-18

# Ethos Technologies - PRIVACY POLICY

|  | 

This website is administered by Ethos. The primary purpose of ethos.com.cn is to be a dynamic resource and business tool offer information regarding our company. Ethos is committed to protecting your privacy. 

This policy lets you know how we collect data, why we collect it, and what choices you have concerning its use. 

### What information do we gather?

Information on ethos.com.cn is gathered in two ways: (1) indirectly (for example, through our site's technology); and (2) directly (for example, when you provide information on various pages of ethos.com.cn). 

One example of information we collect indirectly is through our Internet access logs. When you access ethos.com.cn, your Internet address is automatically collected and is placed in our Internet access logs. 

We collect information directly from you in a number of ways, some of which we describe in this privacy Statement. One way is through the use of cookies. Cookies are small files of information which save and retrieve information about your visit to ethos.com.cn—for example, how you entered our site, how you navigated through the site, and what information was of interest to you. The cookies we use identify you merely as a number. (If you are uncomfortable regarding cookies use, please keep in mind you can disable cookies on your computer by changing the settings in preferences or options menu in your browser.) 

We also collect information when you voluntarily submit it to us. Throughout our site, we provide the opportunity to submit e-mail addresses or other information. It is completely up to you whether or not you want to provide it. 

### How do we use this information?

We analyze it to determine what is most effective about our site, to help us identify ways to improve it, and eventually, to determine how we can tailor ethos.com.cn to make it more effective. We may also use data for other purposes, which we would describe to you at the point we collect the information. 

### Will we share this with outside parties?

As a global organization, data we collect may be transferred internationally throughout Ethos’ worldwide organization. In addition, it may be shared with advisors of Ethos for the purpose of improving our site. At no time will individual information be sold. 

### What about sensitive personal data?

We do not seek to collect sensitive personal data through this site and any such collection is purely incidentally. Please do not submit any information with which you do not feel comfortable to share. Ethos will not request personal identity numbers, personal data about personality and private life, racial or ethnic origin, nationality, political opinions, membership of political parties or movements, religious, philosophical or other similar beliefs, membership of a trade union or profession or trade association, physical or mental health, genetic code, addictions, sexual life, property matters or criminal record (including information about suspected criminal activities). 

### Do we give you access to your information?

You are entitled to know whether we hold information about you and, if we do, to have access to that information and require it to be corrected if it is inaccurate. You can do this by e-mailing [hr@ethos.com.cn.](mailto:hr@ethos.com.cn.)

\-- June 30, 2006 

|
